<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_38b0612e-8543-4648-8963-44e670feeb44"><title>Installing the Plant Applications Message Bridge</title><shortdesc>You must install the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph> Message Bridge on the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph> server node to access the real-time updates on the applications in the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/Univ_Client"></ph>.</shortdesc><prolog><author>Sweta Bhagat</author></prolog><taskbody><prereq>GE recommends that the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph> Message Bridge is installed before installing the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/Univ_Client"></ph>. <p conref="t_install_pa_uc_install_upgrade.dita#task_27d742e3-8e6e-425b-aa19-90cabd738cfc/p_a2d2bc6f-045f-4fae-8168-a1af8df9d694"></p></prereq><context id="context_c565d343-7055-4a3e-a013-b61d4f34da65">The <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph> Message Bridge installer installs the following prerequisites:<ul id="ul_da3a4b48-17f3-404c-a509-55ba93eb6205"><li>Erlang OTP</li><li>RabbitMQ Server</li></ul><note>If the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph> Message Bridge is currently installed, do not reinstall the Message Bridge. You can verify whether the Message Bridge is installed in the <wintitle>Programs and Features</wintitle> list on your computer as shown in the following image.<fig><image href="pa_message_bridge_status.png"/></fig>
            </note></context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Select the <wintitle>Plant Applications Message Bridge</wintitle> wizard, and, on the welcome screen, select <uicontrol>Next</uicontrol> to install the Message Bridge.</cmd><info>
                    <fig id="fig_9d75ca3d-9fd1-4fbe-9e8d-f25dafb42179"><image href="message_bridge.png" id="image_c29482d8-2317-42eb-ab5c-f7bc7bb77fd4"/></fig>
                </info><stepresult>The <wintitle>Missing Prerequisites</wintitle> screen appears, listing any prerequisites that must be installed.<fig id="fig_73d23eaf-86b8-4adf-8b6b-5d227276712f"><image href="mb_missing_prereq.png" id="image_f4fe40ca-7dda-4160-8434-1e30285b2f3c"/></fig></stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Missing Prerequisites</wintitle> screen, select <uicontrol>Continue</uicontrol> to install any missing prerequisites.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Read and accept the license agreement to continue</wintitle> screen appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Read the license agreement, select <uicontrol>Accept</uicontrol>, and then select <uicontrol>Next</uicontrol> to continue the installation.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Microsoft SQL Server Credentials</wintitle> screen appears.<fig id="fig_0711e2d4-5f45-4d41-a8df-4b72fef571ad"><image href="mb_mssql_cred.png" id="image_06888a8e-1be0-464a-b1c4-eed5d3bb6808"/></fig></stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Microsoft SQL Server Credentials</wintitle> screen, enter the credentials to access the Microsoft SQL server as described in the following table.</cmd><choicetable relcolwidth="1* 1*" frame="all"><chhead><choptionhd>Credential</choptionhd><chdeschd>Description</chdeschd></chhead><chrow><choption>Hostname</choption><chdesc>Enter the host name where the Microsoft SQL server is installed in the format <codeph>HOST_NAME\INSTANCE</codeph>, where <codeph>HOST_NAME</codeph> is the host name (either a fully qualified domain name or IP address, of the server), and <codeph>INSTANCE</codeph> is the instance of the server.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>Database</choption><chdesc>Enter the name of the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph> database that you want to connect with the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/Univ_Client"></ph>.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>User</choption><chdesc>Enter the user name that has permissions to access the database you entered in the <uicontrol>Database</uicontrol> box. By default, the user name appears as <codeph>sa</codeph>.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>Password</choption><chdesc>Enter the password for the user you entered in the <uicontrol>User</uicontrol> box.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>Instance</choption><chdesc>Enter the name of the instance of the SQL server. Entering an instance is optional.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>Port</choption><chdesc>Enter the number of the port that the instance uses to listen for client connections.</chdesc></chrow></choicetable></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Validate Connection</uicontrol> to validate the database connection.</cmd><stepresult>If the database connection is successfully validated, the <uicontrol>Next</uicontrol> button is enabled.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Next</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>RabbitMQ Administrator Account Credentials</wintitle> screen appears.<image href="mb_rabbitmq_cred.png" id="image_d0928508-21c8-48b4-b463-fcad13383530"/></stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the  <wintitle>RabbitMQ Administrator Account Credentials</wintitle> section, enter the user name and password for an existing RabbitMQ Administrator, if RabbitMQ is already installed. Else, provide the user name and password you intend to use as an administrator.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Plant Applications Administrator Account Credentials</wintitle> section, enter the user name and password for an administrator account in <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph>, and then select <uicontrol>Validate Connection</uicontrol> to validate the credentials.</cmd><stepresult>If the credentials are successfully validated, the <uicontrol>Next</uicontrol> button is enabled.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Next</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>You are ready to install</wintitle> screen appears.<fig id="fig_95890772-840b-412e-a8c5-bf6adcdeb5d4"><image href="mb_ready_install.png" id="image_e51f9592-9ea7-4b14-b15d-ea371eefe937"/></fig></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Install</uicontrol> to install all the prerequisites and the Message Bridge. </cmd><info>Depending on the options selected, the installation process may take some time. The installer displays the status updates. </info><stepresult>On successful installation, the <wintitle>Installation Successful</wintitle> screen appears.<fig id="fig_ab5311b9-3879-4f03-a9d8-8b29bdce8934"><image href="mb_install_success.png" id="image_df3c9eee-2277-42f8-a238-329af5de034a"/></fig></stepresult></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>Select <uicontrol>View Logs</uicontrol> to see the installation details.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Installation Successful</wintitle> screen, select <uicontrol>Exit</uicontrol> to close the wizard.</cmd></step></steps><result>The Message Bridge is successfully installed on your computer.</result><postreq>After you install the Message Bridge, complete the following procedure to enable the Proficy Server Manager service to pass messages between the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph>:<ol><li>Configure your Administrator user in RabbitMQ. For more information, refer to the  <xref href="t_gsg_configuring_user_in_RabbitMQ.dita#task_f9611437-b4a1-4e60-824a-d43da907f529"></xref> topic.</li><li>Restart the Proficy Server Manager service to automatically start the Proficy Server Message Bridge service.</li></ol><p>The Proficy Server Message Bridge service allows messages to pass between the <ph conref="r_plant_apps_conref.dita#reference_9b9c235a-fb71-4e98-9898-6c28c79ffedd/plant_apps"></ph> clients.</p></postreq></taskbody></task>