<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_5db6686b-fb93-4e1b-8c78-a3225bad268f"><title>Install Docker and Set up the Requirements</title><prolog><author>Reshma Mohammed</author></prolog><taskbody><context id="context_7e42cfd0-faf1-44f4-956c-8259ef93f179"/><steps id="steps_c7e95549-b2f6-4615-bd13-b6e7c0de1032"><step><cmd>Download the Docker application version 18.0 or later from <xref scope="external" format="exe" href="https://download.docker.com/win/stable/Docker%20for%20Windows%20Installer.exe"/>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Follow the install wizard to accept the license, authorize the installer, and proceed with the installation.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Right-click the <uicontrol>Docker</uicontrol> icon in the task bar and select <uicontrol>Settings</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>General</wintitle> screen appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Shared Drives</wintitle> screen, select the <uicontrol>C</uicontrol> drive as your preferred local drive for the container. If you do not select the C drive, an error message appears that there is not enough memory while launching the Plant Applications services. <image scale="70" href="docker_shared_drives.jpg"/></cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Advanced</wintitle> screen, specify <uicontrol>CPUs</uicontrol> as 4 and <uicontrol>Memory</uicontrol> as 22 GB. This is necessary to have enough space to run the Docker images. <image scale="70" href="doc_advanced.PNG"/></cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Proxies</wintitle> screen, select the <uicontrol>Manual proxy configuration</uicontrol> radio button and enter the proxy settings of your environment. By default, the <uicontrol>No Proxy</uicontrol> radio button is selected.</cmd><info><note> In the <uicontrol>bypass for hosts and domains</uicontrol> box, you must add the IP address of your DTR machine, if you want to use the existing DTR account. </note><image scale="70" href="docker_proxies.jpg"/></info></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>Daemon</uicontrol> screen, Specify the IP address of your machine in the <uicontrol>Insecure Registries</uicontrol> box for creating a local DTR account. <image scale="70" href="docker_daemon.jpg"/></cmd></step><step><cmd>Click <uicontrol>Apply</uicontrol>. </cmd></step></steps><result id="result_ad327872-3568-46a3-9188-71e2270ddcca">The Docker settings are saved. </result><postreq id="postreq_927e2d39-3076-43d4-b22e-f2c611403bf3">Install <xref href="t_pa_gsg_doc_install_universal_client_docker_on_windows.dita">Plant Applications Universal Client Docker</xref> to access the Plant Applications.</postreq></taskbody></task>