<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN" "concept.dtd" [
]>
<concept id="concept_d698e2c0-2512-49ba-adfc-1ebd1ea6ac57"><title>About Completing an Operation</title><conbody><p>An operation is completed when all the activities or jobs associated with the operation are completed. As an operator, you can complete an operation only when one or more of the following conditions are true:<ol><li><xref href="t_op_clock_on_an_operation.dita">The operation is clocked on</xref> and is in the In Progress status. You can also clock on an operation from the <wintitle>Search</wintitle> window.</li><li><xref href="t_consume_a_lot.dita">The BOM parts required to complete the operation are consumed</xref>. Only if all the mandatory BOM items have been consumed for all the serial numbers, you can mark the operation complete.</li><li>All the <xref href="c_op_about_quality_data.dita">quality variable specifications</xref> associated with the operation are met. </li><li>If needed, you can <xref scope="external" format="html" href="https://apps-docsstaging.predix.io/en-US/content/manufacturing_solutions/plant_applications/apphub_pa_universal_client_help_discrete/create-a-defect#task_03cbbb59-6044-4ff3-83d8-0ef099db44e1">create a defect</xref> for the serial number.</li><li><xref href="t_op_complete_an_operation.dita">Mark the operation as complete</xref>. </li></ol><note>The <image href="complete-active.png"/> button is available only when these conditions are met. When an operation is clocked on by multiple operators and an operator completes the operation, the operation is marked as Complete for all the operators.</note></p><p>After all the operations in a work order are completed, the work order is marked complete in the Plant Applications Universal Client. You can view the completion status of the work order in <xref scope="external" format="html" href="https://apps-docsstaging.predix.io/en-US/content/manufacturing_solutions/plant_applications/apphub_pa_universal_client_help_discrete/overview#concept_c958454e-0f67-44e6-a341-2e7081190704">Order Management</xref>.</p></conbody></concept>