<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN" "concept.dtd" [
]>
<concept id="concept_a6170f7e-dab3-4add-b372-e4d8ee009605"><title>About Work Orders</title><conbody><p>A work order is a request to manufacture a certain quantity of products in a given time. The work orders are grouped by product and are assigned to a specific Production Line for manufacturing. Depending on the quantity of the product to be manufactured, serial numbers are created in the ERP system.</p><p>Each row in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/supervisor_app"></ph> application represents a work order and are imported from the Plant Applications database by using the Plant Applications Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) scheduler and import services. For more information, refer to the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/erp_guide"></ph>. You can use the  <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/supervisor_app"></ph> application to perform the following tasks.<ul><li><xref href="t_access_a_work_order.dita">Access a Work Order</xref></li><li><xref href="t_search_for_a_work_order.dita">Search for a Work Order</xref></li></ul></p><p>The status of a work order indicates the progress of work for the serial number and the operation, respectively. The following table provides a list of status indicators defined for a work order. <table frame="all"><title>Work Order Status Indicators</title><tgroup cols="3"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="newCol2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="3"/><thead><row><entry>Status </entry><entry>Status Indicator</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>Ready</entry><entry><image href="ready_status.png"/></entry><entry>Indicate that the work order is ready to be executed.</entry></row><row><entry>In Progress</entry><entry><image href="in_progress_icon.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the work on a lot associated with a work order is in progress. This status indicator appears when an operation associated with the work order is clocked on when executing the work order.</entry></row><row><entry>On Hold</entry><entry><image href="on_hold_icon.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the lot associated with a work order is put on hold. This status indicator appears when a defect was created on an operation. After the defect is closed, the status of the operation is modified to the In Progress status and the operation appears in the <wintitle>Released</wintitle> page.</entry></row><row><entry>Completed</entry><entry><image href="complete_icon.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that all the operations associated with the lot are completed.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></p></conbody></concept>