<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN" "concept.dtd" [
]>
<concept id="concept_9e0c28ad-9203-40ce-a380-7322fd75a836"><title>About Operations</title><conbody><p>To manufacture each type of product, a sequence of steps must be performed. Each task or a set of tasks is called an operation. </p><section>
            <title>Operation Status Indicators</title>
            <p>The following table describes the color-coded status indicators of a serial number that appear in the <ph>Order Management</ph> application.</p>
            <p>
                <simpletable relcolwidth="1* 1*" frame="all"><sthead><stentry>Status Indicator</stentry><stentry>Description</stentry></sthead><strow><stentry><image href="ready_status.png"/></stentry><stentry>Indicates that the operation is in the Ready status. This status indicator appears when a work order is ready to be executed.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry><image href="in_progress_icon.png"/></stentry><stentry>Indicates that the operation is in the In Progress status. This status indicator appears when an operation is clocked off, meaning you must clock on the operation before executing the operation. </stentry></strow><strow><stentry><image href="on_hold_icon.png"/></stentry><stentry>Indicates that the operation is in the On Hold status. This status indicator appears when a defect was created on an operation. After the defect is closed, the status of the operation is modified to the In Progress status and the operation appears in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry><image href="su_cancelled_icon.png"/></stentry><stentry>Indicates that the operation is in the Cancelled status. This status indicator appears when operation is cancelled on a Production Line.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry><image href="su_not_ready_icon.png"/></stentry><stentry>Indicates that the operation is in the Not Ready status. This status indicator appears when the work on a work order has not started.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry><image href="su_scrapped.png"/></stentry><stentry>Indicates that the operation is in the Scrapped status. This status indicator appears when the work on a work order has not started.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry><image href="complete_icon.png"/></stentry><stentry>Indicates that the operation is in the Complete status. This status indicator appears when an operation and the quality variables associated with the operation is completed.</stentry></strow></simpletable>
            </p>
        </section></conbody></concept>