<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN" "concept.dtd" [
]>
<concept id="concept_88549408-e316-4fa1-beac-b6a6ace23e9d"><title>About the Status of a Serial Number and an Operation</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><conbody><p>The status of an operation indicates the progress of work for the operation. </p><p>The status of a serial number indicates the progress of work on the serial number <i>for that specific operation</i>. For example, suppose a work order includes performing operations 1 and 2. If operation 1 has been completed for a serial number, the status of the serial number for operation 1 is <i>complete</i>. If operation 2 is yet to begin on the same serial number, the status of the serial number for operation 2 is <i>ready</i>.</p><p>In the Work Queue module, the status of a serial number or an operation is automatically determined and displayed with a color-coded indicator. The following table provides a list of status indicators defined for a serial number and an operation.<table frame="all"><tgroup cols="4"><colspec colname="newCol1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><colspec colname="newCol3" colwidth="1*" colnum="3"/><colspec colname="newCol4" colwidth="1*" colnum="4"/><thead><row><entry>Status</entry><entry>Status Indicator</entry><entry>Description for a Serial Number</entry><entry>Description for an Operation</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>Not ready</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_Not_Ready.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the serial number is not available for you to clock on (for example, the job is still undergoing the previous operation). </entry><entry>Indicates that none of the serial numbers is available for you to perform the operation.</entry></row><row><entry>Cancelled</entry><entry><image href="mes_workorder_cancelled.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the work for the serial number has been cancelled. This happens if a defect has been created for the serial number, and the disposition provided in NCR Management is Scrapped.</entry><entry>Not applicable</entry></row><row><entry>Ready</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_Ready.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the serial number is available for you to perform the operation.</entry><entry>Indicates that at least one serial number in the operation is available for you to perform the operation, and the operation is not in progress for any of the serial numbers.</entry></row><row><entry>Clocked on by you</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_Only_You_Clocked_On.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that only you have clocked on the serial number.</entry><entry>Indicates that only you have clocked on at least one serial number in the operation, and none of the serial numbers in the operation are clocked on by others.</entry></row><row><entry>Clocked on by another user</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_Someone_Else_Clocked_On.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that you have clocked off the serial number.</entry><entry>Indicates that you have clocked off the serial numbers in the operation.</entry></row><row><entry>Clocked on by other users</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_Others_Clocked_On.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that you have clocked off the serial number, and other users have either clocked on or clocked off the serial number.</entry><entry>Indicates that multiple other users have clocked on or clocked off the operation, and you have not clocked on any of the serial numbers in the operation.</entry></row><row><entry>Clocked on by you and other users</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_You_and_Others_Clocked_On.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the serial number is clocked on by you and other users.</entry><entry>Indicates that the serial numbers in the operation are clocked on by you and other users.</entry></row><row><entry>Clocked on by other users in the past</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_Someone_Clocked_On_in_the_Past.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the serial number was clocked on in the past, but is now clocked off.</entry><entry>Indicates that at least one serial number in the operation was clocked on in the past by others, but is now clocked off, and, currently, no serial number in the operation is clocked on.</entry></row><row><entry>On hold</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_On_Hold.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the serial number is on hold. This status indicator appears if a defect has been created for the serial number. After the defect is closed, the status is changed to in progress.</entry><entry>Not applicable</entry></row><row><entry>Complete</entry><entry><image href="S.No_State_Complete.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the serial number is complete.</entry><entry>Indicates that the operation is complete (that is, all the serial numbers in the operation are either complete or scrapped). <note>When an operation is complete, it no longer appears in the work queue.</note></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></p></conbody></concept>