<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_43a64e38-9f13-49c2-9782-eb01e0b756f1"><title>Add a Product-Change Event</title><prolog><author>Sweta Bhagat</author></prolog><taskbody><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Log in to the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client"></ph>. </cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="app_icon_activities.png"/>.</cmd><stepresult>
                    <p>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears.</p>
                </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page, select <image href="header_add_icon_downtime.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>Product Change Event</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Add Product Change</wintitle> window appears, displaying a list of Production Units on which you to want to make a new product. The Production Units that you can access are configured in the Plant Applications Administrator. </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>1. Choose Activity</uicontrol> section, select a Production Unit to create a Product Change event on the selected Production Unit.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>2. Add Event Details</uicontrol> section, in the <uicontrol>PRODUCT GROUP</uicontrol> box, select the product group containing the product you want to make in the Production Unit. </cmd><info>
                    <note type="tip">In the <uicontrol>PRODUCT GROUP</uicontrol> box, you can select <uicontrol>All Products</uicontrol> if you are not sure you about the product group.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>PRODUCT</uicontrol> box, select the product you want to make by using the selected Production Unit.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>TIMESTAMP</uicontrol> box, enter the date and time from when you want to initiate the product change event on the selected Production Unit. </cmd><info>By default, the current date and time appears in the <uicontrol>TIMESTAMP</uicontrol> box. You can select the date and time by using the following options:<ul><li>Select <image href="date_selection_icon_downtime.png"/> to select the date by using a calendar picker, or in the text box next to <image href="date_selection_icon_downtime.png"/> you can manually enter the date in the format yyyy/mm/dd (for example, 2018/11/21).</li><li>In the text box next to <image href="time_icon_downtime.png"/>, enter the time in the format hh:mm:ss (for example, 5:03:44).</li></ul></info></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>In the <wintitle>PRODUCT CHANGE HISTORY</wintitle> section, refer to a history of all product changes on the selected Production Unit with a time stamp when the product was changed was made.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The product change event is created for the Production Unit in the Plant Applications Administrator. In the Plant Applications Administrator, if the option to create activities is enabled in the Display associated with the Production Unit, then the activity associated with the product change event appears in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page. You can then <xref href="t_complete_an_activity.dita#task_c4276b3f-f20b-4bef-9cc9-3569e8711cf3">complete the activity</xref> in the Activities application.</result></taskbody></task>