<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_0e7694e1-ed08-4425-a174-0584cae2442a"><title>Access a BOM Part</title><prolog><author>Reshma Mohammed</author></prolog><taskbody><context id="context_53bf9c44-9bec-430c-949d-730069460e86">An operation contains a list of parts necessary to execute an operation. As an operator, you can access the <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application to consume the BOM parts in a Production Unit.</context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app_ui"></uicontrol>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>Machines</uicontrol> drop-down list box, select a machine.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears, displaying a list of operations associated with the selected machine.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page, select an operation, and then select the <uicontrol>BOM</uicontrol> tab.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section appears, displaying the BOM parts associated with the selected operation.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Refer to each field for a BOM part that appears in the <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section as described in the following table.</cmd><info>
                    <table><tgroup cols="2"><thead><row><entry>Field</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>ORDER</entry><entry>The recommended order of consumption of the BOM part in an operation.</entry></row><row><entry>PART#</entry><entry>The BOM part number associated with the consumable material lots.</entry></row><row><entry>DESCRIPTION</entry><entry>The description of the BOM part.</entry></row><row><entry>REQ QTY</entry><entry>The planned quantity of the BOM parts required for the completion of an operation.</entry></row><row><entry>CONSUMED QTY</entry><entry>The actual quantity of the BOM parts consumed during the production.</entry></row><row><entry>UOM</entry><entry>The unit of measure (UOM) of the BOM part. </entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>
                </info><info>
                    <note type="tip">In the <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section, you can resize the field (column heading) in the grid using a drag-and-drop operation. You can also hover over the field (column heading) until <image href="ncm_resize.png" id="image_2a6d4132-ccd3-43c8-b3dc-38c78cb6d19d"/> appears to resize the width of the field column in the grid table.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section, select a part.</cmd><stepresult>The page containing the part details and consumption history appears.</stepresult></step></steps><result>The BOM parts for the selected operation appear in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application.</result></taskbody></task>