<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_5cc10e29-c36a-45ae-be08-0e4ec0f569ce"><title>Access the Completed or Skipped Activities</title><prolog><author>Sweta Bhagat</author></prolog><taskbody><context>To access the completed or skipped activities, you must have the operator or supervisor role assigned to your user ID.</context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Log in to the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client"></ph>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="app_icon_activities.png"/>. </cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the <uicontrol>Completed</uicontrol> tab to access all the activities that were completed or skipped.</cmd><stepresult>
                    <p>By default, the option to automatically refresh activities in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page is disabled. You can switch the toggle to enable or disable the option to automatically refresh the page as described in the following table. After you select an option, your selection is saved.<table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Option</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><image href="toggle_icon_downtime.png"/></entry><entry>When this option is selected:<ul><li>If <image href="header_update_icon_downtime.png"/> appears in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page, additional completed or skipped activities are available in the shift. Select <image href="header_update_icon_downtime.png"/> to refresh the page and access all the completed or skipped activities.</li><li>If <image href="header_update_icon_downtime.png"/> appears in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page, no additional completed or skipped activities are available to access. </li><li>If <image href="rabbitMQ_down_activities.png"/> appears in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page, the RabbitMQ service is down. </li></ul>
                                        </entry></row><row><entry><image href="toggle_on_icon_downtime.png"/></entry><entry>When this option is selected:<ul><li>If <image href="header_update_icon_downtime.png"/> appears in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page, the manual refresh option is disabled. The page automatically refreshes when an additional completed or skipped activity is available.</li><li>If <image href="rabbitMQ_down_activities.png"/> appears in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page, the RabbitMQ service is down. </li></ul>
                                        </entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>
                    </p>
                    <p>In the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page, you can select <image href="add_comment_icon_activities.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>Add Comment</uicontrol> to add a comment for the activity. If a comment already exists for an activity, select <image href="edit_comment_icon_activities.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>Add/Edit Comment</uicontrol> to add a General comment and access, modify, or delete a general, overdue, or skip comment. For more information, refer to the following topics:<ul><li><xref href="t_access_comments_for_an_activity.dita#task_90c06a7f-aed1-48f9-9e02-3fecc804cd9b"></xref></li><li><xref href="t_add_a_general_comment_for_an_activity.dita#task_a52f44e4-20b5-4435-aef9-866cbd6aab16"></xref></li><li><xref href="t_modify_an_existing_general_comment_for_an_activity.dita#task_549425f3-2e62-448c-acd9-83e027d27d8a"></xref></li><li><xref href="t_modify_an_overdue_comment.dita#task_cbbf653a-90d7-49a4-bbec-13f7bbae6469"></xref></li><li><xref href="t_delete_an_existing_general_comment_for_an_activity.dita#task_2a82e664-a33d-45d3-8fba-c9edb5af7cd1"></xref></li><li><xref href="t_delete_an_overdue_comment.dita#task_33debf73-3682-4047-8dfa-ddc9f858f1d8"></xref></li><li><xref href="t_skip_an_activity.dita#task_86ae0481-4110-4e03-a303-46e823be48d9"></xref></li></ul><note>To modify or delete comments, your role must have appropriate rights configured in the Plant Applications Administrator.</note></p>
                    <p>The following table describes all the fields for an activity that appear in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page.<table colsep="1" rowsep="1" frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Field</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><uicontrol>Activity</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the name of the activity. The default format for the activity name is in the Plant Applications Administrator.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>Time Completed</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the date and time when the activity was completed. The date and time is displayed in the format mm/dd hh:mm (for example, 03/27 13:05).</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>Duration</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the time taken to complete the activity. The duration is displayed in the format hh:mm:ss (for example, 02:00:21).</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>% Complete</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the completion status of the activity as a percentage.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>User</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the ID of the user who completed or skipped the activity.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>Event Type</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the event type associated with the activity.</entry></row><row><entry><b>Equipment</b></entry><entry>Displays the equipment type.</entry></row><row><entry><b>Status</b></entry><entry>Displays the completion status of the activity as a percentage.</entry></row><row><entry><b>Process Order</b></entry><entry>Displays the process order type.</entry></row><row><entry><b>Product</b></entry><entry>Displays the product types.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></p>
                    <p>You can hover over an activity in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page to access the following information about the activity:<ul><li><wintitle>Time</wintitle>: Displays the time when the activity was created.</li><li><uicontrol>Product</uicontrol>: Displays the product associated with the activity.</li><li><uicontrol>Equipment</uicontrol>: Displays the equipment associated with the activity.</li><li><uicontrol>Process Order</uicontrol>: Displays the process order, if available, associated with the activity.</li></ul></p>
                </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>View by</wintitle> box, select an option to access closed activities grouped according to the selected option as described in the following table.</cmd><info>
                    <table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><thead><row><entry>Option</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>Activity</entry><entry>Select to access a list of all completed activities. This option is selected by default.</entry></row><row><entry>Product</entry><entry> Select to access a list of all completed activities grouped by the product types.</entry></row><row><entry>Process Order</entry><entry>Select to access a list of all completed activities grouped by the process order types.</entry></row><row><entry>Equipment</entry><entry>Select to access a list of all completed activities grouped by the equipment types.</entry></row><row><entry>Event</entry><entry>Select to access a list of all completed activities grouped by the event types.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>  
                </info><info>
                    <note>If you select the <uicontrol>Open</uicontrol> tab in the Activities application, and then select the <uicontrol>Completed</uicontrol> tab, the grouping of the page items by the option you selected in the <uicontrol>View by</uicontrol> box and the selection of the active page number are retained. </note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>In the drop-down list box next to the <uicontrol>View by</uicontrol> box, select a time range as described in the following table.</cmd><info>
                    <table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><thead><row><entry>Option</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>Previous Day</entry><entry>Select to access all completed activities from the day prior to the current Production Day.</entry></row><row><entry>Current Day</entry><entry>Select to access all completed activities from the start time until the end time of the current Production Day. If there are no shifts configured for the plant, this option is selected by default.</entry></row><row><entry>Current Shift</entry><entry>Select to access all completed activities from the start time until the end time of the ongoing shift. If shifts are configured for the plant, this option is selected by default.</entry></row><row><entry>Previous Shift</entry><entry>Select to access all completed activities from the shift prior to the current shift. </entry></row><row><entry>Last 7 days</entry><entry>Select to access all completed activities within seven days prior to the current Production Day. <note>This option appears only for the completed activities.</note></entry></row><row><entry>Custom</entry><entry>Select to access all completed activities within a date and time range of up to seven days that you specify by using a calendar window. <note>This option appears only for the completed activities.</note><p>The following calendar window appears when you select the <uicontrol>Custom</uicontrol> option. </p><p><image href="custom_calender_equipment.png"/></p><p>To specify a custom date and time range in the calendar window:<ol><li>In the <wintitle>START DATETIME</wintitle> section, select a date and enter a time in the format hh:mm:ss.</li><li>In the <wintitle>END DATETIME</wintitle> section, select a date and enter a time in the format hh:mm:ss.<note>The end date must be within seven days of the start date.</note></li><li>Select <uicontrol>Apply</uicontrol>.</li></ol></p></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>
                </info><info>
                    <note>The <uicontrol>Previous Shift</uicontrol> and <uicontrol>Current Shift</uicontrol> options appear only when shifts are defined for the display in the Plant Applications Administrator.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select an activity to access the page displaying the Autolog history. </cmd><stepresult>
                    <p>In the page displaying the Autolog history, you can access the overall details of the event associated with an activity and a maximum of 20 historical values of Autolog variables entered for the event at different durations when the activity was scheduled. If an activity associated with an event was skipped, no values are displayed for the Autolog variables.</p>
                    <p>The following table describes each field for an event that appears in the page displaying the Autolog history.<table colsep="1" rowsep="1" frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Field</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><b>Event Name</b></entry><entry>Displays the unique ID of the event.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>Date</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the current date and time in the format dd/mm/yyyy hh:mm:ss (for example, 27/03/2018 10:58:29).</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>Process Order</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the process order associated with the event.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>Product</uicontrol></entry><entry>Displays the product associated with the process order.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></p>
                    <p>In the page displaying the Autolog history, you can select any of the three views based on the specifications:<ul><li><b>Data</b>: Displays only the Autolog variable details.</li><li><b>Spec</b>: Displays only the Autolog variable box is colored according to the specification limits for the Autolog variable as configured in the Plant Applications Administrator.</li><li><b>Data &amp; Spec</b>: Displays the Autolog variable details along with the background color according to the specification limits. <note>The background of an Autolog variable box is colored according to the specification limits for the Autolog variable as configured in the Plant Applications Administrator.</note></li></ul></p>
                    <p>You can select <uicontrol>View Legend</uicontrol> to access all specification limits and the colors associated with them. The available specification limits are:<ul><li><uicontrol>Reject</uicontrol></li><li><uicontrol>Warning</uicontrol></li><li><uicontrol>Target</uicontrol></li><li><uicontrol>User</uicontrol></li><li><uicontrol>Unavailable</uicontrol></li></ul>In the page displaying the Autolog history, you can select an Autolog variable to access information for that Autolog variable. If the specification limits for an Autolog variable are available, the following information appears:<ul><li>The lower and upper specification limits</li><li>The specification limit associated with the variable based on the value entered for the variable</li><li>The threshold value based on whether the entered value is higher or lower than the target value</li></ul></p>
                </stepresult></step></steps></taskbody></task>