<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_a000e4af-9e58-4ce3-b64a-1d7e22ea9d4f"><title>Add a User-Defined Event</title><prolog><author>Sweta Bhagat</author></prolog><taskbody><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Log in to the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client"></ph>. </cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="app_icon_activities.png"/>.</cmd><stepresult>
                    <p>By default, the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears.</p>
                </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page, select <image href="header_add_icon_downtime.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>User Defined Event</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Add User Defined Event</wintitle> window appears, displaying a list of user-defined Autolog sheets accessible to the logged-in user as configured in the Plant Applications Administrator. </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <b>1. Choose activity</b> section, select an activity to create a user-defined event on the selected activity.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>2. Add Event Details</uicontrol> section, in the <uicontrol>EVENT NUMBER</uicontrol> box, enter an event number that is unique and not already added to the database.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>DURATION</uicontrol> box, select a start and end time for the production-based event. </cmd><info>
                    <note>The start and end time of the event must be within two hours from the current date and time.</note>
                </info></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>Specify values for the following optional properties: STATUS, APPLIED PRODUCT, and COMMENT.</cmd><info>
                    <note>When the status of a user-defined event associated with the activity is set to a production status that has the <uicontrol>Lock Event Data</uicontrol> option enabled, you do not have the privilege to modify the Autolog sheet for that event.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>REASONS</uicontrol> box, select a reason to create a user-defined event.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The user-defined event for the selected activity is added and an activity is automatically created for the event. The activity appears in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page.</result></taskbody></task>