<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_etc_2w5_qfb"><title>Consume a Lot</title><prolog><author>Reshma Mohammed</author></prolog><taskbody><context>Consuming a lot represents the process of utilizing a BOM part within an operation. As an operator, you can access the <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application to consume the lots while executing an operation. </context><prereq>You must clock on an operation to consume a lot.</prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app_ui"></uicontrol>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>Machines</uicontrol> drop-down list box, select a machine.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears, displaying a list of operations associated with the selected machine.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page, select an operation, and then select the <uicontrol>BOM</uicontrol> tab.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section appears, displaying the BOM parts associated with the selected operation.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section, select a BOM part.</cmd><stepresult>The page containing the selected BOM part details appears.<note type="tip">You can access the consumption history of the BOM parts in the <wintitle>Consumed History</wintitle> section.</note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> box, enter the serial number or lot number of the BOM part that you want to consume in the operation. Alternatively, to search for a lot by using a barcode, select <image href="scan_icon.png" id="image_f3cea45e-e1fc-48c7-b1bb-c3b57d069e22"/>, and then scan for the barcode of the lot associated with the BOM part. The <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application supports the barcodes of standards Code 39 and Code 128 only.</cmd><info>
                    <note>The <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> box and the <image href="scan_icon.png"/> button are available only when the operation associated with the BOM part is clocked on. Else, you can access only the Consumed History for that BOM part. The search result of the <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> box is not case-sensitive.</note>
                </info><stepresult>The Available: <varname>&lt;quantity_of_parts></varname> message displays the quantity of BOM parts available in the lot for consumption. If the required quantity of the BOM parts specified in the <uicontrol>REQUIRED QTY</uicontrol> box is less than or equal to the quantity available in the lot, the Available: <varname>&lt;quantity_of_parts></varname> message appears in grey, else the message appears in red. In the <uicontrol>REQUIRED QTY</uicontrol> box, if you enter a lot number of a lot that is unavailable in the Plant Applications database or enter a value more than the available quantity in the lot, an informational message appears in red as described in the following table. <simpletable relcolwidth="1* 1* 1*" frame="all"><sthead><stentry>Informational Message Name</stentry><stentry>Message Condition</stentry><stentry>Corrective Actions</stentry></sthead><strow><stentry>Available:<varname> &lt;quantity_of_parts></varname></stentry><stentry>The available quantity in the lot is lesser than the required quantity specified in the <uicontrol>REQUIRED QTY</uicontrol> box.</stentry><stentry>Do one of the following tasks:<ul><li>Consume the available quantity of the BOM part from the existing lot, and then consume the remaining quantity from another lot.</li><li>Search for another lot that contains the total required quantity of the BOM part, and then consume the BOM part. </li></ul></stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Serial/Lot Not Found</stentry><stentry>The lot number or serial number is invalid. </stentry><stentry>Ensure that the lot is available in the database. You can create a lot on a machine and then consume the BOM parts from the lot. For more information, refer to the <xref href="t_op_create_a_lot.dita#task_e8e94348-1fa1-4f88-a22d-0cc56c87b2d9"></xref> topic. </stentry></strow><strow><stentry>This serial/lot is currently not available. Production status = consumed,Current quantity = <varname>&lt;value></varname>.</stentry><stentry>The lot is not available in the database for consumption.</stentry><stentry>Search for another lot that contains BOM parts, and then consume the BOM part.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Lot identifier is found but not available for consumption</stentry><stentry>The selected lot does not contain BOM parts to consume.</stentry><stentry>Search for another lot that contains BOM parts, and then consume the BOM part.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Serial/lot does not match the material being consumed</stentry><stentry>The BOM part material differs from the material in the lot being consumed.</stentry><stentry>Ensure that the material in the BOM part and lot is identical.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Duplicate record found. Unable to consume.</stentry><stentry>More than one record or duplicate records are available for the same lot in the Production Unit. You cannot consume a BOM part from a lot with duplicate records in an operation. </stentry><stentry>Ensure that there are no duplicate records in the selected lot.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Unit of measure of the serial/lot does not match unit of measure for required quantity.</stentry><stentry>The unit of measure (UOM) of the BOM part and the lot is different.</stentry><stentry>Ensure that the UOM of the BOM part and the lot is same.</stentry></strow></simpletable><note>An error message appears when the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application is unable to retrieve the lots for consumption from the Plant Applications database. </note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>QTY TO CONSUME</uicontrol> box, enter the quantity of the BOM parts you want to consume in the operation.</cmd><info>
                    <note>The quantity must be a positive integer. If you enter a value less than or equal to zero in the <uicontrol>QTY TO CONSUME</uicontrol> box, an informational message appears indicating that you must enter a value greater than zero. </note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Consume</uicontrol>.</cmd><info>
                    <note>If you select <uicontrol>Consume</uicontrol> without entering the quantity of the BOM parts you want to consume in the <uicontrol>QTY TO CONSUME</uicontrol> box, an error message appears in red indicating that you must enter a valid serial or lot number in the <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> box. </note>
                </info><stepresult>An entry for the consumption of the material is added to the table in the <wintitle>Consumed History</wintitle> section. In case you consume more than one lot for an operation, the number of entries in the <wintitle>Consumed History</wintitle> section depends on the number of lots that are consumed. After an entry is created in the <wintitle>Consumed History</wintitle> section, you cannot cancel the consumption of the BOM part. If there are any issues in the <wintitle>Consumed History</wintitle> section, contact your Administrator through the Plant Applications Administrator Client. </stepresult></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>Select the <varname>PART#</varname> links in the page displaying BOM part details to navigate to the previous and next BOM parts in a sequential order of the BOM parts.</cmd></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>In the <uicontrol>JUMP TO PART NUMBER</uicontrol> box, specify the part number that you want to locate and then press the Enter key on the keyboard. You must enter the complete part number in the search box and the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application displays only the BOM part that contains the search text. Alternatively, to search for a BOM part by using a barcode, select <image href="scan_icon.png"/>, and then scan for the barcode of the BOM part. The <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application supports the barcodes of standards Code 39 and Code 128 only.</cmd><stepresult>The page containing the selected BOM part details appears. </stepresult></step></steps><result>The BOM parts are consumed in the selected operation, and the quantity of the material consumed appears in the CONSUMED QTY field in the <wintitle>BOM</wintitle> section in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application. </result></taskbody></task>