<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_c4276b3f-f20b-4bef-9cc9-3569e8711cf3"><title>Complete an Activity</title><prolog><author>Sweta Bhagat</author></prolog><taskbody><context>You can complete an activity that is still open by entering values for Autolog variables in the Autolog sheet that appears in the <wintitle>Activity</wintitle> section.</context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Log in to the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client"></ph>. </cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="app_icon_activities.png"/>. </cmd><stepresult>
                    <p>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears.</p>
                </stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Perform</uicontrol> for the activity you want to complete.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Activity</wintitle> section appears in addition to a section displaying information about the activity.<p>The fields in the section displaying information about the activity are described in the following table.<table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Field</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>Date</entry><entry>Displays the date when you started to perform the activity. The locale settings of your computer determine the display format for the date.</entry></row><row><entry>Time</entry><entry>Displays the time on the specified date when you started to perform the activity. The locale settings of your computer determine the display format for the time.</entry></row><row><entry>Process Order</entry><entry>Displays the process order, if available, associated with the activity.</entry></row><row><entry>Product</entry><entry>Displays the product associated with the activity.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></p><p>In the <wintitle>Activity</wintitle> section, the Autolog sheet for the associated Display appears. You configure Display in the Plant Applications Administrator. If the Engineering Units property is enabled for the Display associated with the event, the units of measurement defined for variables also appear next to the variable value in the <wintitle>Activity</wintitle> section. </p><p>In the <wintitle>Activity</wintitle> section, the icons as described in the following table appear.<table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Icon</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><image href="quartile_view_icon_activities.png"/></entry><entry>Select to <xref href="c_about_statistical__analysis_of_variables.dita#concept_e48a8196-24c9-48b0-bd91-f53e113d7b6b">statistically analyze an Autolog variable value</xref> in the Quartile view. </entry></row><row><entry><image href="whisker_chart_icon_activities.png"/></entry><entry>Select to <xref href="c_about_statistical__analysis_of_variables.dita#concept_e48a8196-24c9-48b0-bd91-f53e113d7b6b">statistically analyze an Autolog variable value</xref> in a Whisker chart. By default, the Whisker chart appears in the pane in the Autolog sheet window.</entry></row><row><entry><image href="custom_form_icon_activities.png"/></entry><entry>Select to <xref href="c_about_accessing_a_custom_form.dita#concept_19cf4d4c-f57e-45da-9056-724924f08e38">access a custom form</xref>.<note>This icon appears only if you have configured the Display associated with the activity to enable a custom form to appear in the pane. In this case, by default, the custom form appears in the pane. </note></entry></row><row><entry><image href="column_filter_icon_downtime.png"/></entry><entry>Select to filter a variable associated with the activity. If you select this option, the <uicontrol>Variable Name</uicontrol> box appears. You can then enter the search text in the box, and then select <uicontrol>Apply</uicontrol> to filter a variable. All variables that match with any of the strings in the search text appear in the search results. </entry></row><row><entry><image href="toggle_off_icon_activities.png"/></entry><entry/></row></tbody></tgroup></table>If the scroll type of the variables view is set to pagination, the variables view in the <wintitle>Activity</wintitle> section appears paginated according to the title of the variables group.</p>
                </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the Autolog sheet, enter data for all modifiable Autolog variables. </cmd><info>The application validates the entered values based on the data type, and, if configured in the Plant Applications Administrator, based on the Upper Entry and Lower Entry limits for the variables.<note type="note">
                        <p>You can enter values for Autolog variables available in the Plant Applications Administrator only. Depending on the following configurations in the Plant Applications Administrator, you can enter values for the modifiable variables:<ul><li>When the status of a production-based or user-defined event associated with the activity is set to a production status that has the <uicontrol>Lock Event Data</uicontrol> option enabled, you do not have the privilege to modify the Autolog sheet for that event.</li><li>When the display associated with the activity has the <uicontrol>LockUnavailableCells</uicontrol> display option enabled, the only users who are members of the Administrator Security Group with an Access Level other than Read can enter values for the modifiable Autolog variables that have no available data.</li></ul></p>
                    </note></info></step><step><cmd>Press Tab to save the value.</cmd><info>
                    <p>Whether you enter the value in the Display associated with the Autolog sheet in the Plant Applications Administrator or in the window displaying the Autolog sheet in the Activities application, the last entered variable value is updated automatically in the Autolog sheet.</p>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Back</uicontrol>.</cmd><info>The behavior of the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page and the percentage completion of the activity is based on the criteria and the <uicontrol>Auto Complete Display</uicontrol> display option as described in the following table. You set the <uicontrol>Auto Complete Display</uicontrol> display option for the Display associated with the activity in the Plant Applications Administrator.<table frame="all"><tgroup cols="4"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="newCol2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="3"/><colspec colname="newCol4" colwidth="1*" colnum="4"/><thead><row><entry>Criteria</entry><entry>Auto Complete Display Option Value</entry><entry>Behavior</entry><entry>Percentage Completion Calculation</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>
                                        <ul><li>No sampling interval or test frequency set for variables associated with the time-based events</li><li>No test frequency set for variables associated with the production-based or user-defined events</li></ul>
                                    </entry><entry>False</entry><entry>The <uicontrol>Complete</uicontrol> option appears for that activity. You can then select the <uicontrol>Complete</uicontrol> option to complete the activity. The activity then appears in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page.</entry><entry>The ratio of the total variables for which you entered values to the total variables. </entry></row><row><entry>
                                        <ul><li>No sampling interval or test frequency set for variables associated with the time-based events</li><li>No test frequency set for variables associated with the production-based or user-defined events</li></ul>
                                    </entry><entry>True</entry><entry>If you enter values for:<ul><li>Only a few selected Autolog variables in an activity, the <uicontrol>Complete</uicontrol> option appears for that activity. You can select <uicontrol>Complete</uicontrol> to complete the activity. The activity then appears in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page.</li><li>All modifiable Autolog variables in an activity, the activity is automatically completed and appears in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page. </li></ul>
                                    </entry><entry>The ratio of the total variables for which you entered values to the total variables. </entry></row><row><entry>
                                        <ul><li>Sampling interval or test frequency is set for variables associated with the time-based events</li><li>Test frequency is set for variables associated with the production-based or user-defined events</li></ul>
                                    </entry><entry>False</entry><entry>If you enter values for:<ul><li>Only a few selected modifiable Autolog variables in an activity, the <uicontrol>In Progress</uicontrol> option appears for that activity. You can select <uicontrol>In Progress</uicontrol>, and then enter values for the remaining modifiable Autolog variables.</li><li>All modifiable Autolog variables in an activity, the <uicontrol>Complete</uicontrol> option appears for that activity. You can then select the <uicontrol>Complete</uicontrol> option to complete the activity. The activity then appears in the <wintitle>Completed</wintitle> page.</li></ul>
                                    </entry><entry>The ratio of the total variables with a test ID for which you entered values to the total variables with a test ID.</entry></row><row><entry>
                                        <ul><li>Sampling interval or test frequency is set for variables associated with the time-based events</li><li>Test frequency is set for variables associated with the production-based or user-defined events</li></ul>
                                    </entry><entry>True</entry><entry>If you enter values for:<ul><li>Only a few selected modifiable Autolog variables in an activity, the <uicontrol>In Progress</uicontrol> option appears for that activity. You can select <uicontrol>In Progress</uicontrol>, and then enter values for the remaining modifiable Autolog variables</li><li>All applicable Autolog variables in an activity, the activity is automatically moved to the <wintitle>Complete</wintitle> page.</li></ul>
                                    </entry><entry>The ratio of the total variables with a test ID for which you entered values to the total variables with a test ID.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table><note>If the activity is overdue and the option to enter overdue comments for an activity is required, the window for entering overdue comments appears. In the window for entering overdue comments, you must enter your comment about the overdue activity in the <uicontrol>ADD OVERDUE COMMENT</uicontrol> box, and then select <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol>. </note></info></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>Select <image href="add_comment_icon_activities.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>Add Comment</uicontrol> to enter a comment for a modifiable variable. For more information, refer to the <xref href="t_add_a_variable_comment.dita#task_6f391999-a641-45e3-b07f-92185f2ef4de"></xref> topic.</cmd><info>
                    <note>
                        <p>If comments already exist for a variable, <image href="edit_comment_icon_activities.png"/> appears for the variable. </p>
                    </note>
                </info><stepresult>In the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page, an informational message appears, stating that the comment was successfully added.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the <wintitle>Event</wintitle> tab.</cmd><info>
                    <note>This step is applicable only when the activity is associated with a production-based or user-defined event.</note>
                </info><stepresult>For an activity associated with a production-based event, the following table describes fields that appear in the <wintitle>Event</wintitle>  section.<table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Field</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>EVENT NUMBER</entry><entry>Displays the unique ID of the event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>START TIME</entry><entry>Displays the time when the production started for the event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>END TIME</entry><entry>Displays the time when the production stopped for the event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>EVENT STATUS</entry><entry>Displays the disposition status of the event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>PRODUCT</entry><entry>Displays the product associated with the event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>APPLIED PRODUCT</entry><entry>Displays the product actually associated with the event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>DIMENSION NAME</entry><entry>Displays the dimension of the event as configured in the Plant Applications Administrator. This field is non-modifiable.</entry></row><row><entry>UNITS</entry><entry>Displays the equipment that produced (or contains) the production-based event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>INITIAL</entry><entry>Displays the initial value of the dimension. The value in this field appears blank if you do not modify the dimension value. This field is non-modifiable.</entry></row><row><entry>FINAL</entry><entry>Displays the current value of the dimension.  You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>ADD BATCH COMMENT</entry><entry>Displays the option to add a comment or modify or delete comments for the event. Depending on the security levels defined for your role, you can add, modify, or delete comments.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>For an activity associated with a user-defined event, the following table describes fields that appear in the <wintitle>Event</wintitle>  section.<table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Field</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>EVENT NUMBER</entry><entry>Displays the unique ID of the event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>START TIME</entry><entry>Displays the time when you started the user-defined event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>END TIME</entry><entry>Displays the time when the you stopped the user-defined event. You can modify the value entered in this field.</entry></row><row><entry>L1</entry><entry>Displays the reason for creating the user-defined event. You can modify the value entered in this field.<note>You configure the reason tree for a user-defined event in the Plant Applications Administrator</note></entry></row><row><entry>L2, L3, L4</entry><entry>Display the subreasons, if available, associated with the reason entered for the user-defined event. You can modify the value entered in these fields.</entry></row><row><entry>ADD COMMENT</entry><entry>Displays the option to add a comment or modify or delete comments for the event. You can modify or delete only those comments that were added by you.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></stepresult></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>In the <wintitle>Event</wintitle> section, enter the required value in the modifiable fields, and then select <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol>.</cmd><info>
                    <note>The <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol> option is enabled only when you modify a value for a field.</note>
                </info></step></steps><result>The activity is completed and appears in the <wintitle>Complete</wintitle> page.</result></taskbody></task>