<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_cbbf653a-90d7-49a4-bbec-13f7bbae6469"><title>Modify an Existing Overdue Comment for an Activity</title><shortdesc/><prolog><author>Sweta Bhagat</author></prolog><taskbody><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Log in to the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client"></ph>. </cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="app_icon_activities.png"/>. </cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the tab that includes the activity for which you want to modify the overdue comment.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="edit_comment_icon_activities.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>Add/Edit Comment</uicontrol> for the activity. </cmd><stepresult>A list of all existing comments appears in the window for entering comments.<note type="tip">Alternatively, for open activities, in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page, you can select the time in the <wintitle>Due In</wintitle> row for an overdue activity. All overdue comments appear in the list of comments in the window for entering comments. Skip step 5 if you use this navigation.</note></stepresult></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>In the window for entering general comments, select the <uicontrol>Overdue</uicontrol> check box to filter comments in the existing comments list by the overdue type. </cmd><stepresult>All overdue comments appear in the existing comments list in the window for entering comments.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="edit_icon_activities.png"/> for an existing overdue comment.</cmd><stepresult>The <uicontrol>EDIT OVERDUE COMMENT</uicontrol> box appears, displaying the current comment.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Modify the comment, and then select <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>
                    <p>An informational message stating that the comment was successfully modified appears in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page.</p>
                </stepresult></step></steps><result>The changes to the overdue comment are saved.<note>The position of a comment in the comments list remains constant even if you modify the comment later.</note></result></taskbody></task>