<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_84df4ad8-f07e-47e8-90be-7a5e835bdb94"><title>Access Defects in the Submitted Status</title><prolog><author>Sweta Bhagat</author></prolog><taskbody><context>As a uality engineer, you can access defects in the Submitted status in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/ncm_app"></ph> application.<note>As an operator, you create defects in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application. For more information, refer to the <xref href="t_op_create_a_defect.dita#task_c3606276-1fa2-4a43-9b8a-1d87c9e3868a"></xref> topic.</note></context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Log in to the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client_apphub"></ph>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/ncm_app_ui"></uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears, displaying a summary view of a list of defects in the Submitted status in a grid table with a descending sort applied in the MODIFIED ON field (the field values of the latest modified defect with the status corresponding to the selected page appear first in the grid table). The number of defects that appear in a page depends on the resolution of your computer screen.<note type="tip">Select <image href="ncm_refresh.png"/> to retrieve the latest Submitted defects list and their details. Any filter or sort settings in the page are retained even after the page is refreshed.</note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Refer to each non-modifiable field for a defect in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page as described in the following table.</cmd><choicetable relcolwidth="1* 1*" frame="all"><chhead><choptionhd>Field</choptionhd><chdeschd>Description</chdeschd></chhead><chrow><choption>STATUS</choption><chdesc>The status of the defect as Submitted indicated by the color-coded indicator <image href="defect_submitted.png"/>. The Submitted status indicates that the defect is Submitted for a disposition, and you must select a disposition plan for the defect.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>SERIAL/LOT#</choption><chdesc>The material lot number or serial number that was put on hold and associated with the operation on which the defect was created.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>WORK ORDER</choption><chdesc>The unique identifier of the work order associated with the serial or material lot number that was put on hold.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>OPERATION</choption><chdesc>The operation on which the defect was created.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>SUMMARY</choption><chdesc>The defect summary as entered when the defect was created in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app"></ph> application.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>MODIFIED BY</choption><chdesc>The name of the user who last modified the defect.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>MODIFIED ON</choption><chdesc>The time stamp in the format mm/dd hh:mm (for example, 11/14 15:01) when the defect was last modified.</chdesc></chrow><chrow><choption>QTY</choption><chdesc>The affected quantity of material lots or parts included in the operation on which the defect was created.</chdesc></chrow></choicetable><info>
                    <note id="note_1d1dfc12-2650-4a99-8583-ec03f84286de" type="tip">You can drag a field (column heading) to reorder the position in the grid table where you want the field. You can also hover over the field (column heading) until <image href="ncm_resize.png" id="image_2a6d4132-ccd3-43c8-b3dc-38c78cb6d19d"/> appears to resize the width of the field column in the grid table. The settings specific to reordering and resizing columns are applied in that page only and are available even if you access any other application or log out from the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client_apphub"></ph>.</note>
                </info></step><step importance="optional" id="step_d8331068-1c91-44fc-bbaa-27c634c38eab"><cmd>Select a field (column heading) to sort the field values in the ascending (A to Z [case-sensitive] for letters, smallest to largest for numerical data, and oldest to newest for dates) or descending (Z to A [case-sensitive] for letters, largest to smallest for numerical data, and newest to oldest for dates) order.</cmd><info>
                    <note>The sort settings that you apply on a field column is applied in that page only. If you access any other application in the Plant Applications Universal Client, your sort settings are not retained in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/ncm_app"></ph> application.</note>
                </info></step><step importance="optional"><cmd><xref href="t_ncm_filter_a_defect.dita#task_36f8d89b-f54c-4b89-8744-b277e2843dff">Filter a defect</xref>.</cmd></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>Select any field value of a Submitted defect to access the details view of the defect and <xref href="t_ncm_dispose_a_defect.dita#task_d4111dc2-0768-4d9c-b2d1-f2a0a4dcc4c4">dispose a defect in the Submitted status</xref>.</cmd><info>
                    <note>In the details view, you can select a disposition plan for a defect in the Submitted status. </note>
                </info></step></steps><result>The defects in the Submitted status appear in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/ncm_app"></ph> application.</result></taskbody></task>