<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_36f8d89b-f54c-4b89-8744-b277e2843dff"><title>Filter a Defect</title><prolog><author>Sweta Bhagat</author></prolog><taskbody><context>You can filter a defect in the Home page of <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/ncm_app"></ph> application based on the filter criteria you select. <p>The <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/ncm_app"></ph> application pages use the filter indicators as described in the following table. These indicators appear in a field column in the grid table. <table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Indicator</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><image href="filter_ncm.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the filter is not applied on the field column.</entry></row><row><entry><image href="filter_selected_ncm.png"/></entry><entry>Indicates that the filter is applied on the field column.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></p><p>
                <note>The filter that you apply on a field column is applied in that page only. If you access any other application in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client_apphub"></ph>, your filter selections are not retained in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/ncm_app"></ph> application.</note>
            </p></context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Log in to the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/univ_client_apphub"></ph>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/ncm_app"></ph>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="filter_ncm.png"/> for the field column on which you want to apply a filter.</cmd><stepresult>A window containing the following options appear:<ul><li>A list box containing a list of first 20 values available for the selected field with a case-sensitive ascending sort (A to Z [case-sensitive] for letters, and then lowest to highest for numbers). Move the vertical scroll bar in the list box to fetch more available field values. The vertical scroll bar appears when you hover over the list box.</li><li>A <uicontrol>Search</uicontrol> box where you can enter a search text to refine the field values list.</li><li>A <uicontrol>Select All</uicontrol> check box to select all field values including the field records that have no data.</li><li>A <uicontrol>(Blanks)</uicontrol> check box to filter field records that have no data. <note>This check box appears only for the SUMMARY field.</note></li></ul></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the check box corresponding to one or more field values on which you want to filter the defects.</cmd><info>
                    <note type="tip">Alternatively, in the <uicontrol>Search</uicontrol> box, enter search text to refine the field values list that match the search criteria. As you enter characters in the <uicontrol>Search</uicontrol> box, the field values list is automatically filtered to display only values that contain the search text. The matched field values are case-sensitive. A message appears if no field value is available corresponding to the entered search text. To select all field values, select the <uicontrol>Select All</uicontrol> check box.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Apply</uicontrol>.</cmd><info>
                    <note type="tip">Select <uicontrol>Cancel</uicontrol> to delete your selections and go back to the earlier page.</note>
                </info></step></steps><result>The defects based on the applied filter criteria appear in the selected page, and the applied filter indicator <image href="filter_selected_ncm.png"/> appears for the field. You can apply filters on multiple fields in a page to refine the filtered data. <note type="tip">To clear a filter applied on a field, select <image href="filter_selected_ncm.png"/> for the field on which you want to remove the filter. Then, in the window containing the list of field values, clear the selected check boxes, and then select <uicontrol>Apply</uicontrol>. You can also select <image href="filter_selected_ncm.png"/> to modify the applied filter on a field.</note></result></taskbody></task>