<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_9bbdf596-2e07-4d2e-9e0b-c55da3c6ed0d"><title>Access an Operation</title><prolog><author>Reshma Mohammed</author></prolog><taskbody><context id="context_76f9d296-f4fb-4c4e-8197-bda8498a6461">As an operator, you can access the operations in the Ready, In Progress, on Hold, and Completed statuses associated with a machine in the Operations application.</context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app_ui"></uicontrol>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>Machines</uicontrol> drop-down list box, select a machine.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears, displaying a list of on hold operations in a table with an ascending sort applied in the PRIORITY and MODIFIED ON fields (the field values of the operations with highest priority and the latest modified date appear first in the table). The number of operations that appear in a page depends on the resolution of your computer screen.<note type="tip">Select <image href="ncm_refresh.png"/> to manually refresh the list of operations in the <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page. You can resize the field (column heading) in the by using a drag-and-drop operation.</note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Refer to each non-modifiable field that appears in the respective application page as described in the following table.</cmd><info>
                    <table><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="3.07*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Option</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>STATUS</entry><entry>The status of the operation. For more information, refer to the <xref href="c_op_operation_status_indicators.dita"></xref> topic.</entry></row><row><entry>SERIAL/LOT</entry><entry>The lot number or serial number associated with the work order. </entry></row><row><entry>WORK ORDER</entry><entry>The unique identifier of a work order associated with an operation.</entry></row><row><entry>PRI</entry><entry>The order in which the operation must be completed on a machine.</entry></row><row><entry>MATERIAL</entry><entry>The material number associated with the operation. </entry></row><row><entry>OPERATION</entry><entry>The machine associated with an operation.</entry></row><row><entry>MODIFIED ON</entry><entry>The date and time when the operation was last modified. The date and time appear in the format mm/dd hh:mm (for example, 03/27 10:58).</entry></row><row><entry>USER(S)</entry><entry>The name of the user who worked on an operation. If multiple users worked on an operation, the number of users appears in the USER(S) field for that operation. Select <varname>&lt;number_of_users></varname> to access the list of names of the users who worked on an operation. </entry></row><row><entry>ON/OFF</entry><entry>The clock-on or clock-off status of an operation. </entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>
                </info><info>
                    <note>Select <image href="column_chooser.png"/> to show or hide the fields in the table using a drag-and-drop operation.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd importance="optional">Select <image href="sort_icon.png" id="image_wg1_f55_qfb"/> for a field to filter the operations. </cmd></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>Select an operation to access the BOM parts, instruction documents and quality variables associated with the operation.</cmd></step></steps><result id="result_831d4aa0-6753-47fa-a4a9-192916a97afe">The operations appear in the respective application page.</result></taskbody></task>