<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_8ff928da-e355-4f5e-a756-4fa11c49ca12"><title>Search for an Operation</title><prolog><author>Reshma Mohammed</author></prolog><taskbody><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app_ui"></uicontrol>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>Machines</uicontrol> drop-down list box, select a machine.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears. </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the main navigation bar, select <image href="search_icon.png" id="image_426cef6d-7bf9-4b40-97c9-90e0337d49df"/>.</cmd><stepresult>A window containing a list of search options appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Specify the appropriate search options as described in the following table.</cmd><info>
                                                                                                <table id="table_092e0c70-88e8-4c28-86a7-f1c83655394c"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="3.32*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Option</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>SERIAL/LOT</entry><entry>Enter a serial number or lot number to access the associated operations.<note type="tip">To search for an operation using a barcode, select <image href="scan_icon.png" id="image_f3cea45e-e1fc-48c7-b1bb-c3b57d069e22"/>, and then scan for the barcode of the serial number or lot number associated with the operation. The Operations application supports the barcodes of standards Code 39 and Code 128 only.</note></entry></row><row><entry>WORK ORDER</entry><entry>Enter a work order number to access the associated operations. <note type="tip">To search for an operation using a barcode, select <image href="scan_icon.png"/>, and then scan for the barcode of the work order associated with the operation. The Operations application supports the barcodes of standards Code 39 and Code 128 only.</note></entry></row><row><entry>MATERIAL</entry><entry>Select the drop-down list box, and then search for a material to access the associated operations.</entry></row><row><entry>EQUIPMENT</entry><entry>Select the drop-down list box, and then search for an equipment to access the associated operations.</entry></row><row><entry>STATUS</entry><entry>Select the drop-down list box, and then select an operation status to access the associated operations. <note type="tip">You can also clock on an operation using the STATUS field. For more information, refer to the <xref href="t_op_clock_on_an_operation_using_search.dita#task_7c238c9c-7274-4307-a06a-fff763fffce4"></xref> topic.</note>
                                                                                                                                                                                                                        </entry></row><row><entry>Clocked On</entry><entry>Select to access the operations that you have clocked on.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>
                                                                                                </info></step><step><cmd importance="optional">Select <image href="sort_icon.png" id="image_wg1_f55_qfb"/> for a field to filter the operations. For more information, refer to the <xref href="t_op_filter_an_operation.dita#task_8a55dc16-af5f-4a33-81fb-d8ca73c7d1ac">Filter an Operation</xref> topic.</cmd></step></steps><result id="result_a6bed3b6-fc9b-4c1c-96d5-6546ae23aa59">The operations based on the specified search criteria appear. <note type="tip">To clear the results and perform new search, select <uicontrol>Clear Results</uicontrol> in the respective application page.</note></result></taskbody></task>