<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_6d7799ae-93f1-4e2a-bff3-478314a2dc43"><title>Complete an Operation</title><prolog><author>Reshma Mohammed</author></prolog><taskbody><context>
            <p>After you completed working on an operation, you must mark the operation as complete for the corresponding serial number.</p>
            <p>An operation is completed when all the activities or jobs associated with the operation are completed. After all the operations for a work order are marked complete, the work order is marked complete in the Plant Applications. You can view the completion status of the work order in the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/supervisor_app"></ph> application.</p>
        </context><prereq>
            <ol><li><xref href="t_consume_a_lot.dita">Consume all the required BOM parts</xref> for all the serial numbers that you want to mark complete.</li><li><xref href="t_op_specify_a_quality_variable.dita">Specify the Quality Variables</xref> for all the serial numbers that you want to mark complete.</li></ol>
        </prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/operations_app_ui"></uicontrol>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>Machines</uicontrol> drop-down list box, select a machine.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Open</wintitle> page appears, displaying a list of operations for the selected machine. </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the respective application page, select an operation.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Documents</wintitle> section appears, displaying the documents associated with the operation. You can refer to the documents that appear in the <wintitle>Documents</wintitle> section for instructions or any other reference material.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the <image href="complete-active.png"/> button for the operation you want to complete. </cmd></step></steps><result id="result_c2dc3531-0fc7-43e2-a7c6-e26ebdce3d7c">The operation associated with the work order is completed, and the completed operation appears in the <wintitle>Complete</wintitle> page.</result></taskbody></task>