<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_21d6f24b-fabf-4b22-a3f7-fdc8afa5a329"><title>Assign a Property Group</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>
            <p>When you assign a property group to a route, you can provide values for custom properties that are specific to the route. For example, if the route is for assembling a motor, you can provide the assembly line number, types of motors that are normally assembled on the line, and other details specific to the route.</p>
            <p>You can assign a property group to a route or an operation.</p>
        </context><prereq>Ensure that the property group and underlying properties have been defined in the Property Definition module. For more information, refer to <xref href="c_pd_about_property_definition_app.dita">Property Definition</xref>.</prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, select the route to which you want to assign a property group.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Properties</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>A list of property groups assigned to the route appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>If you want to assign a property group to an operation, select the operation. If you want to assign a property group to the route, select <uicontrol>ALL OPERATIONS</uicontrol>.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="add.png"/>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Assign Property Group(s)</wintitle> window appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the check boxes corresponding to the property groups that you want to assign.</cmd><info>
                    <note type="tip">If you want to assign all the property groups, select the check box in the heading.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Assign</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The selected property groups are assigned to the route or operation.<note type="tip"> By default, the latest version of each property is assigned to the route or operation. If you want to assign an earlier version, select <image href="revision.png"/> in the <wintitle>ACTIONS</wintitle> column, and then select the version that you want to assign. </note></result><postreq><xref href="t_rm_provide_property_values.dita">Provide values for each property in the group</xref>. </postreq></taskbody></task>