<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_60503af5-fcd8-4e8c-a335-9299bb81c12e"><title>Attach a Document</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>You can attach a document to an operation or a route so that an operator can refer to it when performing the operation. </context><prereq><xref href="t_rm_upload_document.dita">Upload the document that you want to attach</xref>.</prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, select the route to which you want to attach a document.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Documents</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>A list of documents attached to the route or to an individual operation in the route appears.<note type="tip">You can access a list of documents attached to each operation by selecting the corresponding operation.</note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>If you want to attach the document to the route, select <uicontrol>ALL OPERATIONS</uicontrol>. If you want to attach the document to an operation, select the operation.</cmd><stepresult>A list of documents attached to the route or operation appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="add.png"/>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Attach Documents and/or URLs</wintitle> window appears, displaying a list of documents that are available.<note type="tip">
                        <ul><li>You can preview a document by selecting the URL in the <wintitle>FILE/URL</wintitle> column.</li><li>By default, the latest version of each document appears in the list. If you want to attach a previous version of a document, in the row containing the document, select <image href="revision.png"/>.</li></ul>
                    </note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>In each row containing the document that you want to attach, select the check box.</cmd><info>
                    <note type="tip">You can select all the documents in the list by selecting the check box in the column heading.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Attach</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The document is attached to the route or operation.</result><postreq><xref href="t_rm_assign_property_group.dita">Assign a property group to the route or operation</xref>.</postreq></taskbody></task>