<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_1db20fb6-879d-4432-809e-03f6ceda4fe4"><title>Revise a Route</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, perform one of the following tasks: </cmd><choices><choice>If you want to revise a released route, select <uicontrol>Released</uicontrol>.</choice><choice>If you want to revise an archived route, select <uicontrol>Archived</uicontrol>.</choice></choices></step><step><cmd>Select the route that you want to revise.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>View Route</wintitle> page appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="menu.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>Revision</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Revise Route</wintitle> window appears, displaying the route details. <note> The name, description, production line, material, and BOM formulation are copied from the latest revision of the route. You cannot modify these details. You can add, modify, or remove an operation. You can also assign a different BOM item, equipment, property group, or document.</note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Next</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Edit Route</wintitle> page appears. The operations, resources, BOM items, properties, and documents linked to the route are the same as that of the previous version of the route.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>As needed, add, modify, or remove operations, or assign a different BOM item, property, or document.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The route is revised and is in the draft state. The value in the <uicontrol>REVISION</uicontrol> box is incremented by 1. <note type="tip">To access the revision history of the route, in the <wintitle>Released</wintitle> or <wintitle>Archived</wintitle> section, select <image href="revision.png"/> in the row containing the route.</note>
                                </result></taskbody></task>