<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_6dc26d06-2c07-4cec-ac6d-8aa497781aa0"><title>Copy an Operation</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>This topic describes how to copy an operation. You can also <xref href="t_rm_create_operation.dita">create a new operation</xref>.</context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, select the route in which you want to copy an operation.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Edit Route</wintitle> page appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the left pane, in the row containing the operation that you want to copy, select <image href="copy.png"/>.</cmd><stepresult>A new row for the copied operation appears in the <wintitle>Overview</wintitle> section. <ul><li>The name of the copied operation is in the following format: Copy &lt;name of the original operation></li><li>The remaining columns are populated with the corresponding values in the original operation.</li></ul></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Enter a unique name for the operation. The name must not exceed 100 characters.</cmd></step><step><cmd>As needed, modify values as specified in the following table.</cmd><info><table><tgroup cols="2"><thead><row><entry>Column</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><wintitle>SEQUENCE</wintitle></entry><entry>Identifies the sequence number of the operation. If multiple operations must be performed simultaneously, provide the same sequence number. <note type="tip">When setting the sequence numbers, provide a gap in their values so that you can easily add new operations between other operations. For example, if the sequence number of the first operation is 1, set the sequence number of the second operation to 10. This allows you to add new operations between these two operations without the need to modify the sequence numbers of all the operations.</note></entry></row><row><entry><wintitle>NAME</wintitle></entry><entry>Identifies the name for the operation. Enter a unique name that does not exceed 100 characters.</entry></row><row><entry><wintitle>DESCRIPTION</wintitle></entry><entry>Identifies the description for the operation. Enter a description that does not exceed 1000 characters.</entry></row><row><entry><wintitle>EQUIPMENT</wintitle></entry><entry>Identifies the equipment that is used to perform the operation. You can select multiple pieces of equipment for the same operation, and you can select the same piece of equipment for multiple operations.<note type="tip">You can also select the equipment used in an operation from the <wintitle>Resources</wintitle> section.</note></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The operation is copied.</result><postreq><xref href="t_rm_link_bom_to_operation.dita#task_cb39f132-7681-4a42-9544-3179a1ab509f">Link a BOM item to the operation</xref>.</postreq></taskbody></task>