<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_256c531d-2f37-4c6e-a646-f94bf73156a6"><title>Copy a Route</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>
            <p>A copied route is in the draft state by default, regardless of the state of the original route. When you copy a route, the operations, BOM items, properties, and documents in the route are also copied.</p>
            <p>This topic describes how to copy a route. You can also <xref href="t_rm_add_route.dita">create a new one</xref>.</p>
        </context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, perform one of the following tasks: </cmd><choices><choice>If you want to copy a route in the draft state, select the route that you want to copy.<p>The <wintitle>Edit Route</wintitle> page appears.</p>
                    </choice><choice>If you want to copy a route in the released or archived state, select <uicontrol>Released</uicontrol> or <uicontrol>Archived</uicontrol>, respectively, and then select the route that you want to copy. <p>The <wintitle>View Route</wintitle> page appears.</p>
                    </choice></choices></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="menu.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>Duplicate</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Copy Route</wintitle> window appears. <ul><li>The <uicontrol>NAME</uicontrol> box contains a value in the following format: Copy of &lt;name of the original route></li><li>The <uicontrol>REVISION</uicontrol> box is disabled and populated with the value 1, regardless of the value in the <uicontrol>REVISION</uicontrol> box of the original route. This is because this is the first draft of the copied route.</li><li>The remaining boxes are populated with the corresponding values in the original route. </li></ul></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Enter a unique name for the copied route. The name must not exceed 100 characters.</cmd></step><step><cmd>As needed, modify values in the remaining boxes, and then select <uicontrol>Copy</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The route is copied. You can now add or remove operations, property groups, and documents to the copied route. You can also change the BOM items and equipment linked to the operations.</result></taskbody></task>