<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_55ed9d7c-c81d-4f1d-af43-0bc408ca33d4"><title>Create a Work Order</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, select <uicontrol>Released</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>A list of released routes appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the route for which you want to create a work order.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>View Route</wintitle> page appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="menu.png"/>, and then select <uicontrol>Create Work Order</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Create Work Order</wintitle> window appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Provide values as specified in the following table.</cmd><info>
                    <table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="1*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Box</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><uicontrol>WORK ORDER</uicontrol></entry><entry><p>You must enter a value in this box. Enter a unique name for the work order that does not exceed 100 characters. </p>
                                        <p>If a work order with the same name exists:<ul><li>If the work order is ready, it is deleted and replaced with the one that you are creating.</li><li>If the work order is in progress, you cannot create this work order.</li></ul></p></entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>ORDER QUANTITY</uicontrol></entry><entry>Enter the quantity of the product that must be manufactured as part of the work order. The value in this box must not exceed 100. The value in this box determines the number of rows that appear in the <wintitle>ENTER SERIAL/LOT#</wintitle> section.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>PRIORITY</uicontrol></entry><entry>Enter the priority in which the work order must be completed. <ul><li>If you want to assign the highest priority for the work order, enter 1.</li><li>If you want to assign the lowest priority for the work order, enter 0 or leave the box blank. </li></ul></entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT# PREFIX</uicontrol></entry><entry>Enter the prefix for each serial number in the lot. The value in this box helps identify the serial numbers that belong to the same work order.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>PLAN START</uicontrol></entry><entry>Enter the planned date and time to begin work on the work order.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>PLAN END</uicontrol></entry><entry>Enter the planned date and time to complete the work on the work order. By default, this box is populated with the date and time that is 24 hours from the current date and time.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol></entry><entry>You must enter a value in all the rows. Enter a unique serial number for each lot.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>GENERATED SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol></entry><entry>Identifies the serial number that will be assigned to each lot in the work order. This box is disabled and populated with a combination of the values in the <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT# PREFIX</uicontrol> and <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> boxes.</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Create</uicontrol>.</cmd><info>
                    <note type="tip">If you want to create another work order for the same route, select <uicontrol>Create and Add Another</uicontrol>.</note>
                </info></step></steps><result>The work order is created, and it appears in <xref href="c_sm_about_the_security_management_app.dita">Order Management</xref>.</result></taskbody></task>