<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_b34fa82e-8882-4c84-95f3-86b1271b6574"><title>Upload a New Version of a Document</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>
            <p>Using Route Management, you can maintain the revision history of documents that you upload to the document store. </p>
            <p>You can upload a new version of a document whether or not it is attached to a route or an operation. If the document has already been attached to a route or an operation, after you upload the new version, this newer version is used in the route or the operation. You can, however, use an earlier version of the document if needed.</p>
        </context><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>If the document has been attached to a route or an operation, perform the following steps:</cmd><substeps><substep><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, select the route to which you have attached the document.</cmd></substep><substep><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Documents</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>A list of documents attached to the route or to an individual operation in the route appears.<note type="tip">You can access a list of documents attached to each operation by selecting the corresponding operation.</note></stepresult></substep><substep><cmd>In the row containing the document for which you want to upload a new version, select <image href="upload.png"/>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Upload document</wintitle> window appears. With the exception of the <uicontrol>FILE NAME / URL</uicontrol> box, all the boxes are disabled and populated with values from the previous version of the document.</stepresult></substep><substep><cmd>In the <uicontrol>FILE NAME / URL</uicontrol> box, enter the URL or path to the version of the document that you want to upload. </cmd><info>
                            <note type="tip">If the document is stored in the local machine, you can select <uicontrol>Browse</uicontrol> to go to the path.</note>
                        </info></substep><substep><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Upload</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The new version of the document is uploaded. All the routes and operations to which the document has been attached now use the version that you have uploaded. <note>You can access each version of the document by selecting <image href="revision.png"/> in the row that contains the document. </note></stepresult></substep></substeps></step><step><cmd>If the document has not been attached to a route or an operation, perform the following steps:</cmd><substeps><substep><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, select a route.</cmd></substep><substep><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Documents</uicontrol>.</cmd></substep><substep><cmd>In the upper-right corner of the <wintitle>Documents</wintitle> section, select <image href="upload.png"/>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Upload Document</wintitle> window appears.</stepresult></substep><substep><cmd>Provide the same values as those provided for the previous version of the document, and then select <uicontrol>Upload</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The new version of the document is uploaded. <note>You can access each version of the document by selecting <image href="add.png"/>, and then selecting <image href="revision.png"/> in the window that appears.</note></stepresult></substep></substeps></step></steps></taskbody></task>