<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_61429981-b700-4e0f-a2d9-de72177b339c"><title>Add a Route</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>This topic describes how to create a route. You can also <xref href="t_rm_copy_route.dita">copy an existing one.</xref></context><prereq>
            <p>The following components must exist in the Plant Applications database before you create a route:<ul><li>A production line linked to a single virtual unit</li><li>Material defined for the production line</li><li>BOM formulation defined for the material</li></ul></p>
            <p>If these components do not exist, contact the Plant Applications administrator.</p>
        </prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, select <image href="add.png"/>.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Create Route</wintitle> window appears. The <uicontrol>REVISION</uicontrol> box is disabled and populated with the value 1 because this is the first draft of the route.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Provide values as specified in the following table.</cmd><info> <table><tgroup cols="2"><thead><row><entry>Field</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><uicontrol>NAME</uicontrol></entry><entry>Enter a unique name for the route that does not exceed 100 characters.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>DESCRIPTION</uicontrol></entry><entry>Enter a description for the route that does not exceed 1000 characters.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>PRODUCTION LINE</uicontrol></entry><entry>Select a production line to which the route belongs. This box contains a list of production lines defined in Plant Applications Administrator. A value is required in this field. </entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>MATERIAL</uicontrol></entry><entry>Select the material that you want to use in the route. This box is enabled after you select a value in the <uicontrol>PRODUCTION LINE</uicontrol> box. It contains a list of materials defined for the production line in Plant Applications.</entry></row><row><entry><uicontrol>BOM FORMULATION</uicontrol></entry><entry>Select the BOM formulation that you want to use in the route. This box is enabled after you select a value in the <uicontrol>MATERIAL</uicontrol> box. It contains a list of BOM formulations configured for the material in Plant Applications. </entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Next</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The route is created and is in the draft state. The <wintitle>Edit Route</wintitle> page appears, allowing you to create an operation.</result><postreq><xref href="t_rm_create_operation.dita#task_80b8cd76-31b3-490e-adc8-137bf3fc57e2">Add an operation to the route.</xref></postreq></taskbody></task>