<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_29ec5852-7e50-4681-b8d7-f6f7661779a3"><title>Provide Values for Properties</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>When properties are defined in Plant Applications, default value for each property may be provided. Using Route Management, you can provide values for each property (and overwrite default values if they exist).</context><prereq><xref href="t_rm_assign_property_group.dita">Assign a property group to the route or operation</xref>.</prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Route Management</wintitle> page, select the route for which you want to provide values for properties.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Properties</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>A list of property groups assigned to the route appears.<note type="tip">If the property has been assigned to an operation, you can select the operation to access a list of property groups assigned to the operation (instead of accessing property groups assigned to all the operations in the route).</note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="chevron_right.png"/> corresponding to the property group for which you want to provide values.</cmd><stepresult>A list of properties in the property group appears. If a default value has been provided for a property in the Property Definition module, it appears in the <wintitle>VALUE</wintitle> column.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Enter or modify the value in the <wintitle>VALUE</wintitle> column for each property for which you want to provide a value. The following conditions apply when you provide a value for a property:</cmd><info>
                    <ul><li>If a property has been specified as mandatory in the Property Definition module, you must provide a value for the property.</li><li>The value must be of the same data type as specified in the <wintitle>DATA TYPE</wintitle> column.</li></ul>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol>.</cmd></step></steps><result>The values for the properties are saved.</result><postreq><xref href="c_rm_about_releasing_route.dita">Release the route</xref>.</postreq></taskbody></task>