<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_00978455-8a56-45d2-a5c1-bd2a720dc989"><title>Modify the Planned Start and End dates of a Work Order</title><prolog><author>Reshma Mohammed</author></prolog><taskbody><prereq>You can modify the planned start and end dates of a work order only if it is in the In Progress, Ready, and On Hold state. </prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Order Management</wintitle> page, select a line in the <uicontrol>Line</uicontrol> drop-down list box.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Released</wintitle> page appears, displaying a list of work orders associated with the selected line.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Released</wintitle> page, select a work order in the table.</cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Work Order</wintitle> page appears, displaying the status of the work order.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select <image href="su_edit_icon.png"/> in the navigation bar. </cmd><stepresult>The <wintitle>Edit Work Order</wintitle> window appears, displaying planned start and end dates of the work order. </stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the  box, enter a date and time when the work order is planned to begin.</cmd><info>
                    <note>You can also select <image href="su_calendar_icon.png"/> to select a date and time.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>As needed, modify values in the <uicontrol>PLANNED END DATE</uicontrol>, <uicontrol>PLANNED START DATE</uicontrol> boxes.</cmd><info>
                    <note>You can also select <image href="su_calendar_icon.png"/> to select a date and time.</note>
                </info></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>In the <uicontrol>PRIORITY</uicontrol> box, you can modify the priority of the work order.</cmd><info>
                    <note>The quantity must be a positive integer, where 1 denotes the highest priority and 0 denotes the lowest priority. If you do not enter a value in the <uicontrol>PRIORITY</uicontrol> box for a work order, a message appears indicating that you must enter a value.</note>
                </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Update</uicontrol>. </cmd></step></steps><result>The changes made to the planned start and end dates of the work order are saved.</result></taskbody></task>