<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_bd9c85fc-c3c2-4717-a142-75c6568223e2"><title>Search for a Work Order</title><prolog><author>Reshma Mohammed</author></prolog><taskbody><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Order Management</wintitle> page, select <image href="search_icon.png" id="image_426cef6d-7bf9-4b40-97c9-90e0337d49df"/> in the main navigation bar.</cmd><stepresult>A window containing a list of search options appears.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Specify the appropriate search options as described in the following table. </cmd><info>
                <table><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*" colnum="1"/><colspec colname="c2" colwidth="3.5*" colnum="2"/><thead><row><entry>Field</entry><entry>Description</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>SERIAL/LOT</entry><entry>Enter a serial number or lot number to access the associated work orders. You must enter complete serial number in the <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT</uicontrol> box and the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/supervisor_app"></ph> application displays only the work order that contains the search text. <note type="tip">To search for a work order using a barcode, select <image href="scan_icon.png"/>, and then scan for the barcode of the serial number or lot number associated with the operation. The <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/supervisor_app"></ph> application supports the barcodes of standards Code 39 and Code 128 only.</note></entry></row><row><entry>WORK ORDER</entry><entry>Enter a work order number to access the details of the work order. You must enter the complete work order number in the <uicontrol>WORK ORDER</uicontrol> box and the <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/supervisor_app"></ph> application displays only the work order that contains the search text. <note type="tip">To search for an operation using a barcode, select <image href="scan_icon.png"/>, and then scan for the barcode of the work order associated with the operation. The <ph conref="r_conref_pa.dita#reference_9d772631-a06f-44ea-ae85-bdf4615c2e9f/supervisor_app"></ph> application supports the barcodes of standards Code 39 and Code 128 only.</note></entry></row><row><entry>PRODUCT</entry><entry>Select the drop-down list box, and then search for a product to access the associated work orders.</entry></row><row><entry>STATUS</entry><entry>Select the drop-down list box, and then select a work order status to access the associated work orders. </entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table>
                </info></step><step importance="optional"><cmd>Select <image href="sort_icon.png" id="image_wg1_f55_qfb"/> for a field to filter a work order. For more information, refer to the <xref href="t_filter_a_work_order.dita#task_87ead1e3-6d98-4a4f-bd8d-4189a85010e6"></xref> topic.</cmd></step></steps><result>The work orders based on the specified search criteria appear. <note type="tip">To clear the results and perform new search, select <uicontrol>Clear Results</uicontrol> in the respective application page.</note></result></taskbody></task>