<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_52230e3e-8f5f-4a42-bea4-854d35943f4c"><title>Provide Data for Quality Variables</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>
            <p>Quality variables include details about the data that you must collect while performing an operation. These variables are defined in Plant Applications Administrator. The values that you provide for these variables help verify that the parameters that are critical to the quality and manufacturing processes are within the acceptable limits. You can use this data to review the performance of a production line and production unit and compare the quality of the products produced in each unit with projections for an operation.</p>
            <p>For example, suppose you have been assigned the testing operation in a motor manufacturing unit. Quality variables can include the torque and rpm of the motor shaft. When you test each motor, you must enter the torque and rpm values for the corresponding serial number. A quality supervisor can then verify that the torque and rpm fall within the acceptable range.</p>
            <p>You can provide data for quality variables only for serial numbers that are in progress.</p>
        </context><prereq><xref href="t_wq_clock_on_serial_number.dita">Clock on the serial numbers</xref> for which you want to provide data for quality variables.</prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Work Queue</wintitle> page, select the operation for which you want to provide data for the quality variables.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Quality</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>A list of serial numbers in the operation appear in the left section. </stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the serial number whose data you want to provide.</cmd><stepresult>A list of quality variables defined for the operation appear in the workspace. <note type="tip">
                        <ul><li>By default, only the mandatory quality variables appear. If you want to access all the quality variables, switch the <uicontrol>Dynamic Rows</uicontrol> toggle.</li><li>If you want to view the lowest, highest, lower quartile, upper quartile, and median values for each variable, select <image href="grid_view.png"/>. If you want to view the same values plotted on a chart, select <image href="analysis.png"/>.</li><li>If you want to add a comment, select <image href="list_view.png"/>.</li></ul>
                    </note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>For each variable, enter data in the <wintitle>SPEC</wintitle> column. </cmd><info><note type="tip">If you want to plot the value on a chart, select <image href="analysis.png"/>.</note></info><stepresult>If acceptable limits have been specified for the variable, the box in the <wintitle>SPEC</wintitle> column displays a color, indicating whether the value that you have entered is within the acceptable range.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Repeat steps 3 and 4 for each serial number in the operation.</cmd></step></steps><result>The data for the quality variables is saved.</result><postreq> If a part contains a defect, <xref href="t_wq_create_defect.dita">create a defect</xref>. Otherwise, <xref href="t_wq_mark_operation_complete.dita">mark the operation complete for the serial number</xref>.</postreq></taskbody></task>