<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA General Task//EN" "generalTask.dtd" [
]>
<task id="task_4458b9ee-8427-4ce2-b187-2fb75d9ed1ca"><title>Specify Consumption of BOM Items for an Operation</title><prolog><author>Swathi</author></prolog><taskbody><context>
                                 <p>Consuming a BOM item represents the process of utilizing a BOM item within an operation. The BOM items required to complete an operation are defined in the Route Management module or in the ERP system, along with details on whether using a BOM item is mandatory to complete the operation. </p>
                                 <p>Using the Work Queue module, you can specify the quantity of BOM items that have been consumed for each serial number. You can complete an operation only if all the required BOM items for each serial number in the operation are consumed.</p>
                      </context><prereq><xref href="t_wq_clock_on_serial_number.dita">Clock on the serial numbers</xref> for which you want to specify BOM consumption.</prereq><steps id="steps_yvq_p11_xw"><step><cmd>In the <wintitle>Work Queue</wintitle> page, select the operation for which you want to specify the consumption of BOM items.</cmd></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>BOM</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>A list of serial numbers appears in the <wintitle>SERIAL NUMBERS</wintitle> subsection. </stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the serial number for which you want to specify the consumption of BOM items.</cmd><stepresult>A list of BOM items for the selected serial number appears in the workspace.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>Select the BOM item whose consumption you want to specify.</cmd><stepresult>A window appears, providing information on the required quantity of the BOM item, whether consuming the BOM item is mandatory to complete the operation, and the quantity that has been already consumed for the serial number.</stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> box, enter the serial number or lot number of the BOM item that you want to consume in the operation. Alternatively, to search for a lot by using a barcode, select <image href="scan_icon.png" id="image_f3cea45e-e1fc-48c7-b1bb-c3b57d069e22"/>, and then scan for the barcode of the lot associated with the BOM item. Only the barcodes of standards Code 39 and Code 128 are supported.</cmd><info>
                                                       <note>The <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> box and the <image href="scan_icon.png"/> button are available only when the operation associated with the BOM item is clocked on. Else, you can access only the consumed history for that BOM item. The search result of the <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> box is not case-sensitive.</note>
                                            </info><stepresult>The Available: <varname>&lt;quantity_of_items></varname> message displays the quantity of BOM items available in the lot for consumption. If the required quantity of the BOM items specified in the <uicontrol>REQUIRED QTY</uicontrol> box is less than or equal to the quantity available in the lot, the Available: <varname>&lt;quantity_of_items></varname> message appears in grey, else the message appears in red. In the <uicontrol>REQUIRED QTY</uicontrol> box, if you enter a lot number of a lot that is unavailable in the Plant Applications database or enter a value more than the available quantity in the lot, an informational message appears in red as described in the following table. <simpletable relcolwidth="1* 1* 1*" frame="all"><sthead><stentry>Informational Message Name</stentry><stentry>Message Condition</stentry><stentry>Corrective Actions</stentry></sthead><strow><stentry>Available:<varname> &lt;quantity_of_items></varname></stentry><stentry>The available quantity in the lot is less than the required quantity specified in the <uicontrol>REQUIRED QTY</uicontrol> box.</stentry><stentry>Do one of the following tasks:<ul><li>Consume the available quantity of the BOM item from the existing lot, and then consume the remaining quantity from another lot.</li><li>Search for another lot that contains the total required quantity of the BOM item, and then consume the BOM item. </li></ul></stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Serial/Lot Not Found</stentry><stentry>The lot number or serial number is invalid. </stentry><stentry>Ensure that the lot is available in the database. You can create a lot on a machine and then consume the BOM items from the lot.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>This serial/lot is currently not available. Production status = consumed,Current quantity = <varname>&lt;value></varname>.</stentry><stentry>The lot is not available in the database for consumption.</stentry><stentry>Search for another lot that contains BOM items, and then consume the BOM item.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Lot identifier is found but not available for consumption</stentry><stentry>The selected lot does not contain BOM items to consume.</stentry><stentry>Search for another lot that contains BOM items, and then consume the BOM item.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Serial/lot does not match the material being consumed</stentry><stentry>The BOM item material differs from the material in the lot being consumed.</stentry><stentry>Ensure that the material in the BOM item and lot are identical.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Duplicate record found. Unable to consume.</stentry><stentry>More than one record or duplicate records are available for the same lot in the Production Unit. You cannot consume a BOM item from a lot with duplicate records in an operation. </stentry><stentry>Ensure that there are no duplicate records in the selected lot.</stentry></strow><strow><stentry>Unit of measure of the serial/lot does not match unit of measure for required quantity.</stentry><stentry>The unit of measure (UOM) of the BOM item and the lot is different.</stentry><stentry>Ensure that the UOM of the BOM item and the lot is same.</stentry></strow></simpletable></stepresult></step><step><cmd>In the <uicontrol>QTY TO CONSUME</uicontrol> box, enter the quantity of consumption of the BOM item. </cmd><choices><choice>If each BOM item has a separate lot number, enter the lot number of each BOM item in the <uicontrol>SERIAL/LOT#</uicontrol> box, and then enter 1 in the <uicontrol>QTY TO CONSUME</uicontrol> box. For example, suppose you have been assigned the motor assembling operation. For the endshields BOM item, since the required quantity is two, you must enter the lot numbers of the two endshields used in the motor. In this case, in the <uicontrol>QTY TO CONSUME</uicontrol> box, enter the value 1 for each wheel.</choice><choice>If the BOM items have a combined lot number, enter the lot number, and then enter the number of BOM items consumed in the <uicontrol>QTY TO CONSUME</uicontrol> box. For example, suppose you have been assigned the motor assembling operation for a motor. If the operation requires four nuts and bolts, enter the lot number for the nuts and bolts BOM item, and then enter 4 in the <uicontrol>QTY TO CONSUME</uicontrol> box.</choice></choices><info>
                                                       <note>If the lot number that you have entered does not exist in Plant Applications, a window appears, asking you whether you want to create the lot number. If that happens, enter the quantity to create and consume, and then select <uicontrol>Yes</uicontrol>. </note>
                                            </info></step><step><cmd>Select <uicontrol>Consume</uicontrol>.</cmd><stepresult>The details of the BOM item consumption are saved, and appear in the <wintitle>Consumed History</wintitle> section.<note type="tip">You can navigate to the next BOM item by selecting the corresponding link. Or, you can skip to any BOM item by entering the serial number of the BOM item or scanning the bar code of the BOM item.</note></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Repeat steps 3 through 6 for each serial number on which you have performed the operation.</cmd></step></steps><postreq><xref href="t_wq_provide_quality_variables_data.dita">Provide data for quality variables</xref> for each serial number in the operation.</postreq></taskbody></task>